If I said there's a magical button here,
if we press it, you never have to call
someone ever again, would you press it?
Yeah, of course.
Then why not? So I bought an Eight Sleep.
It was £4,000 for a mattress cover.
And at first, I was like, "Oh, is
that worth it?" I got onto the website.
They didn't want to do a sales call.
I got to see the product,
see the benefits, see everything about it,
and I made a
decision then whether or not to buy
or not.
And for me,
I didn't need to jump on a call with
someone for four grand.
And that's not just because the level I'm
at, it's also because they gave me a
money-back guarantee. I
was either a happy customer
or I got my money back.
The sales call works because it's what
you're doing all the time, and you're
manually getting there
and calling people
and going through everything.
But in my mind, I'm like,
if we can sell a £4,000 mattress cover
that
regulates your temperature,
why can't we sell £360 worth of coaching
where they can
go, they can see the results,
they can go through it at their own pace?
Because ultimately as well,
I don't particularly want to get on a call
with someone
as a consumer or as someone running a
business.
But also,
the pricing thing to me just feels a bit
deceptive.
Imagine I'm like, "Oh,
you've got to come to this hotel in Dubai.
It's called the Atlantis." "How much
is it?" "Come to the hotel." "No, no,
but how
much?" "You come to the hotel.
Tell you what, stay three nights.
We'll talk when you get here."
And then you get to the reception,
you get there,
and you're like, "What?
It's two grand a night." Now suddenly,
I feel like I've
wasted everyone's time,
and I'm fucking embarrassed.
I might just book a room in the hotel
because I'm embarrassed.
I might be like, "Well, fuck,
I'm here." And I want people to know I'm
expensive.
I want people to know it's a lot of money.
Eight Sleep don't give a fuck their
mattress is four grand because all the
people
that can't afford it are talking about it,
and all the people that can afford it
can. You can do the sales calls
if you want,
but you just told me you didn't enjoy
it. And every part of your business,
I want you to love.
And I think you should show pricing.
Are you good at what you do?
Yes.
Then why is it a problem?